<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<exskills>
	<item>1★</item>
	<item>Tablet of Ruin Lv. 1 - 10% boost to Atk</item>
	<item>Tablet of Protection Lv. 1 - 10% boost to Def</item>
	<item>Tablet of Healing Lv. 1 - 10% boost to Rec</item>
	<item>Tablet of Vitality Lv. 1 - 10% boost to max HP</item>
	<item>Ruinous Spirit Lv. 1 - 15% boost Slightly boosts Atk when HP is full</item>
	<item>Ruinous Ardor Lv. 1 - 15% boost Slightly boosts Atk when BB gauge is full</item>
	<item>Protective Spirit Lv. 1 - 15% boost Slightly boosts Def when HP is full</item>
	<item>Protective Ardor Lv. 1 - 15% boost Slightly boosts Def when BB gauge is full</item>
	<item>Epidemic Tragedy Lv. 1 - 40% boost Slightly boosts damage against status afflicted foes</item>
	<item>2★</item>
	<item>Tablet of Ruin Lv. 2 - 20% boost to Atk</item>
	<item>Tablet of Protection Lv. 2 - 20% boost to Def</item>
	<item>Tablet of Healing Lv. 2 - 20% boost to Rec</item>
	<item>Tablet of Vitality Lv. 2 - 20% boost to max HP</item>
	<item>Destroyer's Authority Lv. 1 - 10% boost to max HP, Atk</item>
	<item>Guardian's Authority Lv. 1 - 10% boost to max HP, Def</item>
	<item>Warrior's Authority Lv. 1 - 10% boost to Atk, Def</item>
	<item>Ruinous Spirit Lv. 2 - 25% boost Boosts Atk when HP is full</item>
	<item>Ruinous Ardor Lv. 2 - 25% boost Boosts Atk when BB gauge is full</item>
	<item>Protective Spirit Lv. 2 - 25% boost Boosts Def when HP is full</item>
	<item>Protective Ardor Lv. 2 - 25% boost Boosts Def when BB gauge is full</item>
	<item>Raging Blade Lv. 1 - 30% boost Slightly boosts Spark damage</item>
	<item>Raging Memories Lv. 1 - 30% boost after 15 Sparks Boosts Spark damage when Sparks have exceeded certain amount (for 2 turns)</item>
	<item>Flashing Light Lv. 1 - 5% boost Slightly boosts critical hit rate</item>
	<item>Flashing Blade Lv. 1 - 30% boost Slightly boosts critical hit damage</item>
	<item>Flashing Spirit Lv. 1 - 1~2 BC Critical damage slightly boosts BB gauge</item>
	<item>Epidemic Tragedy Lv. 2 - 60% boost Boosts damage against status afflicted foes</item>
	<item>Warrior's Command Lv. 1 - 1-3 BC Probable slight BB gauge boost when attacking normally</item>
	<item>Heroic Doctrine Lv. 1 - 3 BC per 5,000 damage Boosts BB gauge when damage taken has exceeded certain amount</item>
	<item>Overwhelming Love Lv. 1 - 1,000 HP for 3 turns per 25 HC Recovers HP when HC collected have exceeded certain amount</item>
	<item>Treasured Abode Lv. 1 - 5% boost Slightly boosts BC, HC drop rate when attacking</item>
	<item>Thief's Warning Lv. 1 - Slightly boosts 5% boost Zel, 2% boost Karma, 1% boost Item drop rate when attacking</item>
	<item>Power of Poison Lv. 1 - 10% chance Low probability of inflicting Poison effect when attacking</item>
	<item>Power of Weak Lv. 1 - 10% chance Low probability of inflicting Weak effect when attacking</item>
	<item>Power of Sick Lv. 1 - 10% chance Low probability of inflicting Sick effect when attacking</item>
	<item>Power of Injury Lv. 1 - 10% chance Low probability of inflicting Injury effect when attacking</item>
	<item>Power of Curse Lv. 1 - 10% chance Low probability of inflicting Curse effect when attacking</item>
	<item>Power of Paralysis Lv. 1 - 10% chance Low probability of inflicting Paralysis effect when attacking</item>
	<item>3★</item>
	<item>Tablet of Ruin Lv. 3 - 30% boost to Atk</item>
	<item>Tablet of Protection Lv. 3 - 30% boost to Def</item>
	<item>Tablet of Healing Lv. 3 - 30% boost to Rec</item>
	<item>Tablet of Vitality Lv. 3 - 30% boost to max HP</item>
	<item>Destroyer's Authority Lv. 2 - 15% boost to max HP, Atk</item>
	<item>Guardian's Authority Lv. 2 - 15% boost to max HP, Def</item>
	<item>Warrior's Authority Lv. 2 - 15% boost to Atk, Def</item>
	<item>Divine Oracle Lv. 1 - 10% boost to Atk, Def, Rec, max HP</item>
	<item>Ruinous Spirit Lv. 3 - 50% boost Greatly boosts Atk when HP is full</item>
	<item>Ruinous Ardor Lv. 3 - 50% boost Greatly boosts Atk when BB gauge is full</item>
	<item>Protective Spirit Lv. 3 - 50% boost Greatly boosts Def when HP is full</item>
	<item>Protective Ardor Lv. 3 - 50% boost Greatly boosts Def when BB gauge is full</item>
	<item>Supreme Spirit Lv. 1 - 15% boost Slightly boosts Atk, Def, Rec when HP is full</item>
	<item>Supreme Ardor Lv. 1 - 15% boost Slightly boosts Atk, Def, Rec when BB gauge is full</item>
	<item>Divine Life Lv. 1 - 10% boost Slightly boosts Atk, Def, Rec when HP is over 50% full</item>
	<item>Divine Wisdom Lv. 1 - 10% boost Slightly boosts Atk, Def, Rec when BB gauge is over 50% full</item>
	<item>Demonic Life Lv. 1 - 15% boost Slightly boosts Atk, Def, Rec when HP is under 50% full</item>
	<item>Demonic Nature Lv. 1 - 15% boost Slightly boosts Atk, Def, Rec when BB gauge is under 50% full</item>
	<item>Glorious Life Lv. 1 - 0.15% boost per 1% HP remaining Slightly boosts Atk, Def, Rec relative to how high remaining HP is</item>
	<item>Rebellious Blood Lv. 1 - 0.15% boost per 1% HP lost Slightly boosts Atk, Def, Rec relative to how low remaining HP is</item>
	<item>Raging Light Lv. 1 - 50% chance to fill 1~2 BC Probable slight BB gauge boost from Spark damage</item>
	<item>Raging Core Lv. 1 - 10% boost Spark damage slightly boosts BC, HC drop rate</item>
	<item>Raging Blade Lv. 2 - 40% boost Boosts Spark damage</item>
	<item>Raging Memories Lv. 2 - 40% boost after 15 Sparks Greatly boosts Spark damage when Sparks have exceeded certain amount (for 2 turns)</item>
	<item>Flashing Light Lv. 2 - 10% boost Boosts critical hit rate</item>
	<item>Flashing Blade Lv. 2 - 50% boost Boosts critical hit damage</item>
	<item>Flashing Spirit Lv. 2 - 2~3 BC Critical damage boosts BB gauge</item>
	<item>Hymn of Awakening Lv. 1 - 25% boost Slightly boosts BB Atk</item>
	<item>Piercing Lv. 1 - 10% chance Low probability of Def ignoring effect when attacking</item>
	<item>Legendary Calamity Lv. 1 - 30% boost Slightly boosts elemental damage</item>
	<item>Epidemic Tragedy Lv. 3 - 80% boost Greatly damage against status afflicted foes</item>
	<item>Demonic Victory Song Lv. 1 - 1 BC Slightly boosts BB gauge each turn</item>
	<item>Warrior's Command Lv. 2 - 2-4 BC Probable BB gauge boost when attacking normally</item>
	<item>Empress's Heartbeat Lv. 1 - 1 BC Probable slight BB gauge boost when attacked</item>
	<item>Prosperous Nobility Lv. 1 - 5% boost Slightly boosts efficacy of BC</item>
	<item>Heroic Doctrine Lv. 2 - 5 BC per 5,000 damage Greatly boosts BB gauge when damage taken has exceeded certain amount</item>
	<item>Healer's Revelation Lv. 1 - 500 + 10% Rec Slightly recovers HP each turn</item>
	<item>Angel Tears Lv. 1 - 25% chance to heal 5% damage Probable slight recovery of HP when attacked</item>
	<item>Demonic Blood Lv. 1 - 2~4% HP drain Slightly absorbs HP when attacking</item>
	<item>Hyperion Lv. 1 - 10% boost Slightly boosts HC efficacy</item>
	<item>Overwhelming Love Lv. 2 - 1,500 HP for 3 turns per 25 HC Greatly recovers HP when HC collected have exceeded certain amount</item>
	<item>Thief's Warning Lv. 2 - Boosts 8% boost Zel, 4% boost Karma, 1% boost Item drop rate when attacking</item>
	<item>Legendary Thief Lv. 1 - Slightly boosts 2% boost BC, HC, Zel, 1% boost Karma, Item drop rate when attacking</item>
	<item>Poison Guard - Negates Poison effect</item>
	<item>Weak Guard - Negates Weak effect</item>
	<item>Sick Guard - Negates Sick effect</item>
	<item>Injury Guard - Negates Injury effect</item>
	<item>Curse Guard - Negates Curse effect</item>
	<item>Paralysis Guard - Negates Paralysis effect</item>
	<item>Power of Poison Lv. 2 - 15% chance Probable infliction of Poison effect when attacking</item>
	<item>Power of Weak Lv. 2 - 15% chance Probable infliction of Weak effect when attacking</item>
	<item>Power of Sick Lv. 2 - 15% chance Probable infliction of Sick effect when attacking</item>
	<item>Power of Injury Lv. 2 - 15% chance Probable infliction of Injury effect when attacking</item>
	<item>Power of Curse Lv. 2 - 15% chance Probable infliction of Curse effect when attacking</item>
	<item>Power of Paralysis Lv. 2 - 15% chance Probable infliction of Paralysis effect when attacking</item>
	<item>Power of Confusion Lv. 1 - 5% chance to inflict Curse/Poison/Paralysis &amp; 7% chance to inflict Sick/Injury/Weak Low probability of inflicting random status ailment when attacking</item>
	<item>Revolution Banner Lv. 1 - 3% chance to inflict Curse/Poison/Paralysis &amp; 5% chance to inflict Sick/Injury/Weak Low probability of inflicting random status ailment when attacked</item>
	<item>Legendary Shield Lv. 1 - Boosts 5% boost damage reduction rate and 2 BC BB gauge while guarding</item>
	<item>Tale of Honor Lv. 1 - 10% boost Boosts OD gauge fill rate</item>
	<item>4★</item>
	<item>Tablet of Ruin Lv. 4 - 40% boost to Atk</item>
	<item>Tablet of Protection Lv. 4 - 40% boost to Def</item>
	<item>Tablet of Healing Lv. 4 - 40% boost to Rec</item>
	<item>Tablet of Vitality Lv. 4 - 40% boost to max HP</item>
	<item>Destroyer's Authority Lv. 3 - 20% boost to max HP, Atk</item>
	<item>Guardian's Authority Lv. 3 - 20% boost to max HP, Def</item>
	<item>Warrior's Authority Lv. 3 - 20% boost to Atk, Def</item>
	<item>Divine Oracle Lv. 2 - 15% boost to Atk, Def, Rec, max HP</item>
	<item>Ruinous Spirit Lv. 4 - 75% boost Hugely boosts Atk when HP is full</item>
	<item>Ruinous Ardor Lv. 4 - 75% boost Hugely boosts Atk when BB gauge is full</item>
	<item>Protective Spirit Lv. 4 - 75% boost Hugely boosts Def when HP is full</item>
	<item>Protective Ardor Lv. 4 - 75% boost Hugely boosts Def when BB gauge is full</item>
	<item>Supreme Spirit Lv. 2 - 25% boost Boosts Atk, Def, Rec when HP is full</item>
	<item>Supreme Ardor Lv. 2 - 25% boost Boosts Atk, Def, Rec when BB gauge is full</item>
	<item>Divine Life Lv. 2 - 20% boost Boosts Atk, Def, Rec when HP is over 50% full</item>
	<item>Divine Wisdom Lv. 2 - 20% boost Boosts Atk, Def, Rec when BB gauge is over 50% full</item>
	<item>Demonic Life Lv. 2 - 25% boost Boosts Atk, Def, Rec when HP is under 50% full</item>
	<item>Demonic Nature Lv. 2 - 25% boost Boosts Atk, Def, Rec when BB gauge is under 50% full</item>
	<item>Glorious Life Lv. 2 - 0.2% boost per 1% HP remaining Boosts Atk, Def, Rec relative to how high remaining HP is</item>
	<item>Rebellious Blood Lv. 2 - 0.25% boost per 1% HP lost Boosts Atk, Def, Rec relative to how low remaining HP is</item>
	<item>Raging Light Lv. 2 - 50% chance to fill 1~3 BC Probable BB gauge boost from Spark damage</item>
	<item>Raging Spirit Lv. 1 - 1 BC Spark damage slightly boosts BB gauge</item>
	<item>Raging Core Lv. 2 - 15% boost Spark damage boosts BC, HC drop rate</item>
	<item>Raging Blade Lv. 3 - 50% boost Greatly boosts Spark damage</item>
	<item>Raging Memories Lv. 3 - 60% boost after 15 Sparks Hugely boosts Spark damage when Sparks have exceeded certain amount (for 2 turns)</item>
	<item>Flashing Light Lv. 3 - 15% boost Greatly boosts critical hit rate</item>
	<item>Flashing Blade Lv. 3 - 70% boost Greatly boosts critical hit damage</item>
	<item>Flashing Spirit Lv. 3 - 3~4 BC Critical damage greatly boosts BB gauge</item>
	<item>Hymn of Awakening Lv. 2 - 50% boost Boosts BB Atk</item>
	<item>Piercing Lv. 2 - 20% chance Probable Def ignoring effect when attacking</item>
	<item>Legendary Calamity Lv. 2 - 50% boost Boosts elemental damage</item>
	<item>Epidemic Tragedy Lv. 4 - 100% boost Hugely damage against status afflicted foes</item>
	<item>Demonic Victory Song Lv. 2 - 2 BC Boosts BB gauge each turn</item>
	<item>Warrior's Command Lv. 3 - 3-6 BC Probable great BB gauge boost when attacking normally</item>
	<item>Empress's Heartbeat Lv. 2 - 1-2 BC Probable BB gauge boost when attacked</item>
	<item>Prosperous Nobility Lv. 2 - 10% boost Boosts efficacy of BC</item>
	<item>Heroic Doctrine Lv. 3 - 7 BC per 5,000 damage Hugely boosts BB gauge when damage taken has exceeded certain amount</item>
	<item>Healer's Revelation Lv. 2 - 800 + 10% Rec Recovers HP each turn</item>
	<item>Angel Tears Lv. 2 - 25% chance to heal 10% damage Probable recovery of HP when attacked</item>
	<item>Demonic Blood Lv. 2 - 5~8% HP drain Slightly absorbs HP when attacking</item>
	<item>Hyperion Lv. 2 - 20% boost Boosts HC efficacy</item>
	<item>Overwhelming Love Lv. 3 - 2,000 HP for 3 turns per 25 HC Hugely recovers HP when HC collected have exceeded certain amount</item>
	<item>Treasured Abode Lv. 2 - 10% boost Boosts BC, HC drop rate when attacking</item>
	<item>Thief's Warning Lv. 3 - Greatly boosts 12% boost Zel, 6% boost Karma, 2% boost Item drop rate when attacking</item>
	<item>Legendary Thief Lv. 2 - Boosts 4% boost BC, HC, Zel, 2% boost Karma, 1% boost Item drop rate when attacking</item>
	<item>Poison, Injury, Weak Guard - Negates Poison, Injury, Weak effects</item>
	<item>Curse, Paralysis, Sick Guard - Negates Curse, Paralysis, Sick effects</item>
	<item>Power of Poison Lv. 3 - 20% chance High probability of inflicting Poison effect when attacking</item>
	<item>Power of Weak Lv. 3 - 20% chance High probability of inflicting Weak effect when attacking</item>
	<item>Power of Sick Lv. 3 - 20% chance High probability of inflicting Sick effect when attacking</item>
	<item>Power of Injury Lv. 3 - 20% chance High probability of inflicting Injury effect when attacking</item>
	<item>Power of Curse Lv. 3 - 20% chance High probability of inflicting Curse effect when attacking</item>
	<item>Power of Paralysis Lv. 3 - 20% chance High probability of inflicting Paralysis effect when attacking</item>
	<item>Power of Confusion Lv. 2 - 7% chance to inflict Curse/Poison/Paralysis &amp; 10% chance to inflict Sick/Injury/Weak Probable infliction of random status ailment when attacking</item>
	<item>Revolution Banner Lv. 2 - 5% chance to inflict Curse/Poison/Paralysis &amp; 8% chance to inflict Sick/Injury/Weak Probable infliction of random status ailment when attacked</item>
	<item>Iron Shield - Negates Def ignoring damage</item>
	<item>Divine Fortune - Negates critical damage</item>
	<item>Tale of Honor Lv. 2 - 20% boost Greatly boosts OD gauge fill rate</item>
	<item>5★</item>
	<item>Tablet of Ruin Lv. 5 - 50% boost to Atk</item>
	<item>Tablet of Protection Lv. 5 - 50% boost to Def</item>
	<item>Tablet of Healing Lv. 5 - 50% boost to Rec</item>
	<item>Tablet of Vitality Lv. 5 - 50% boost to max HP</item>
	<item>Destroyer's Authority Lv. 4 - 30% boost to max HP, Atk</item>
	<item>Guardian's Authority Lv. 4 - 30% boost to max HP, Def</item>
	<item>Warrior's Authority Lv. 4 - 30% boost to Atk, Def</item>
	<item>Divine Oracle Lv. 3 - 20% boost to Atk, Def, Rec, max HP</item>
	<item>Fire Oracle Lv. 1 - 20% boost to Atk, Def, Rec, max HP of Fire types</item>
	<item>Water Oracle Lv. 1 - 20% boost to Atk, Def, Rec, max HP of Water types</item>
	<item>Earth Oracle Lv. 1 - 20% boost to Atk, Def, Rec, max HP of Earth types</item>
	<item>Thunder Oracle Lv. 1 - 20% boost to Atk, Def, Rec, max HP of Thunder types</item>
	<item>Light Oracle Lv. 1 - 20% boost to Atk, Def, Rec, max HP of Light types</item>
	<item>Dark Oracle Lv. 1 - 20% boost to Atk, Def, Rec, max HP of Dark types</item>
	<item>Bravery Oracle Lv. 1 - 20% boost to Atk, Def, Rec, max HP of male Units</item>
	<item>Compassion Oracle Lv. 1 - 20% boost to Atk, Def, Rec, max HP of female Units</item>
	<item>Fortitude Oracle Lv. 1 - 20% boost to Atk, Def, Rec, max HP of genderless Units</item>
	<item>Lord's Divination Lv. 1 - 20% boost to Atk, Def, Rec, max HP of Lord types</item>
	<item>Anima's Divination Lv. 1 - 20% boost to Atk, Def, Rec, max HP of Anima types</item>
	<item>Breaker's Divination Lv. 1 - 20% boost to Atk, Def, Rec, max HP of Breaker types</item>
	<item>Guardian's Divination Lv. 1 - 20% boost to Atk, Def, Rec, max HP of Guardian types</item>
	<item>Oracle's Divination Lv. 1 - 20% boost to Atk, Def, Rec, max HP of Oracle types</item>
	<item>Ruinous Spirit Lv. 5 - 100% boost Enormously boosts Atk when HP is full</item>
	<item>Ruinous Ardor Lv. 5 - 100% boost Enormously boosts Atk when BB gauge is full</item>
	<item>Protective Spirit Lv. 5 - 100% boost Enormously boosts Def when HP is full</item>
	<item>Protective Ardor Lv. 5 - 100% boost Enormously boosts Def when BB gauge is full</item>
	<item>Supreme Spirit Lv. 3 - 30% boost Greatly Atk, Def, Rec when HP is full</item>
	<item>Supreme Ardor Lv. 3 - 30% boost Greatly boosts Atk, Def, Rec when BB gauge is full</item>
	<item>Divine Life Lv. 3 - 30% boost Greatly boosts Atk, Def, Rec when HP is over 50% full</item>
	<item>Divine Wisdom Lv. 3 - 30% boost Greatly boosts Atk, Def, Rec when BB gauge is over 50% full</item>
	<item>Demonic Life Lv. 3 - 50% boost Greatly boosts Atk, Def, Rec when HP is under 50% full</item>
	<item>Demonic Nature Lv. 3 - 50% boost Greatly boosts Atk, Def, Rec when BB gauge is under 50% full</item>
	<item>Glorious Life Lv. 3 - 0.3% boost per 1% HP remaining Greatly boosts Atk, Def, Rec relative to how high remaining HP is</item>
	<item>Rebellious Blood Lv. 3 - 0.5% boost per 1% HP lost Greatly boosts Atk, Def, Rec relative to how low remaining HP is</item>
	<item>Demigod Balance - 1% boost per 1% HP remaining Boosts Atk relative to how high remaining HP is &amp; 1% boost per 1% HP lost boosts Def relative to how low remaining HP is</item>
	<item>Raging Light Lv. 3 - 50% chance to fill 2~4 BC Probable great BB gauge boost from Spark damage</item>
	<item>Raging Spirit Lv. 2 - 1~2 BC Spark damage boosts BB gauge</item>
	<item>Raging Core Lv. 3 - 20% boost Spark damage greatly boosts BC, HC drop rate</item>
	<item>Raging Blade Lv. 4 - 60% boost Hugely boosts Spark damage</item>
	<item>Raging Memories Lv. 4 - 80% boost after 15 Sparks Enormously boosts Spark damage when Sparks have exceeded certain amount (for 2 turns)</item>
	<item>Flashing Light Lv. 4 - 20% boost Hugely boosts critical hit rate</item>
	<item>Flashing Blade Lv. 4 - 100% boost Hugely boosts critical hit damage</item>
	<item>Flashing Spirit Lv. 4 - 3~5 BC Critical damage hugely boosts BB gauge</item>
	<item>Hymn of Awakening Lv. 2 - 75% boost Greatly boosts BB Atk</item>
	<item>Combat Tempest - +1 to each hit count Raises normal hit amount</item>
	<item>Piercing Lv. 3 - 30% chance High probability of Def ignoring effect when attacking</item>
	<item>Legendary Calamity Lv. 3 - 70% boost Greatly boosts elemental damage</item>
	<item>Epidemic Tragedy Lv. 5 - 120% boost Enormously damage against status afflicted foes</item>
	<item>Demonic Victory Song Lv. 3 - 3 BC Greatly boosts BB gauge each turn</item>
	<item>Warrior's Command Lv. 4 - 4-8 BC Probable huge BB gauge boost when attacking normally</item>
	<item>Empress's Heartbeat Lv. 3 - 1-3 BC Probable great BB gauge boost when attacked</item>
	<item>Prosperous Nobility Lv. 3 - 15% boost Greatly boosts efficacy of BC</item>
	<item>Heroic Doctrine Lv. 4 - 10 BC per 5,000 damage Enormously boosts BB gauge when damage taken has exceeded certain amount</item>
	<item>Healer's Revelation Lv. 3 - 1,000 + 10% Rec Greatly recovers HP each turn</item>
	<item>Angel Tears Lv. 3 - 25% chance to heal 15% damage Probable great recovery of HP when attacked</item>
	<item>Demonic Blood Lv. 3 - 6-10% HP drain Greatly absorbs HP when attacking</item>
	<item>Hyperion Lv. 3 - 30% boost Greatly boosts HC efficacy</item>
	<item>Overwhelming Love Lv. 4 - 2,500 HP for 3 turns per 25 HC Enormously recovers HP when HC collected have exceeded certain amount</item>
	<item>Treasured Abode Lv. 3 - 15% boost Greatly boosts BC, HC drop rate when attacking</item>
	<item>Thief's Warning Lv. 4 - Hugely boosts 15% boost Zel, 8% boost Karma, 2% boost Item drop rate when attacking</item>
	<item>Legendary Thief Lv. 3 - Greatly boosts 6% boost BC, HC, Zel, 3% boost Karma, 1% boost Item drop rate when attacking</item>
	<item>Goddess's Protection - Negates all status ailments</item>
	<item>Hermit's Barrier - Negates Atk, Def, Rec reduction effects</item>
	<item>Power of Confusion Lv. 3 - 10% chance to inflict Curse/Poison/Paralysis &amp; 13% chance to inflict Sick/Injury/Weak High probability of inflicting random status ailment when attacking</item>
	<item>Revolution Banner Lv. 3 - 7% chance to inflict Curse/Poison/Paralysis &amp; 10% chance to inflict Sick/Injury/Weak High probability of inflicting random status ailment when attacked</item>
	<item>Legendary Shield Lv. 2 - Greatly boosts 10% boost damage reduction rate and 3 BC BB gauge while guarding</item>
	<item>Proof of Sanctity - Negates elemental damage</item>
	<item>Tale of Honor Lv. 3 - 30% boost Hugely boosts OD gauge fill rate</item>
	<item>6★</item>
	<item>Tablet of Ruin Lv. 6 - 75% boost to Atk</item>
	<item>Tablet of Protection Lv. 6 - 75% boost to Def</item>
	<item>Tablet of Healing Lv. 6 - 75% boost to Rec</item>
	<item>Tablet of Vitality Lv. 6 - 75% boost to max HP</item>
	<item>Destroyer's Authority Lv. 5 - 40% boost to max HP, Atk</item>
	<item>Guardian's Authority Lv. 5 - 40% boost to max HP, Def</item>
	<item>Warrior's Authority Lv. 5 - 40% boost to Atk, Def</item>
	<item>Divine Oracle Lv. 4 - 25% boost to Atk, Def, Rec, max HP</item>
	<item>Supreme Spirit Lv. 4 - 50% boost Hugely boosts Atk, Def, Rec when HP is full</item>
	<item>Supreme Ardor Lv. 4 - 50% boost Hugely boosts Atk, Def, Rec when BB gauge is full</item>
	<item>Divine Life Lv. 4 - 40% boost Hugely boosts Atk, Def, Rec when HP is over 50% full</item>
	<item>Divine Wisdom Lv. 4 - 40% boost Hugely boosts Atk, Def, Rec when BB gauge is over 50% full</item>
	<item>Demonic Life Lv. 4 - 75% boost Hugely boosts Atk, Def, Rec when HP is under 50% full</item>
	<item>Demonic Nature Lv. 4 - 75% boost Hugely boosts Atk, Def, Rec when BB gauge is under 50% full</item>
	<item>Glorious Life Lv. 4 - 0.5% boost per 1% HP remaining Hugely boosts Atk, Def, Rec relative to how high remaining HP is</item>
	<item>Rebellious Blood Lv. 4 - 0.75% boost per 1% HP lost Hugely boosts Atk, Def, Rec relative to how low remaining HP is</item>
	<item>Raging Light Lv. 4 - 50% chance to fill 2~5 BC Probable huge BB gauge boost from Spark damage</item>
	<item>Raging Spirit Lv. 3 - 1~3 BC Spark damage greatly boosts BB gauge</item>
	<item>Raging Core Lv. 4 - 25% boost Spark damage hugely boosts BC, HC drop rate</item>
	<item>Raging Blade Lv. 5 - 70% boost Enormously boosts Spark damage</item>
	<item>Flashing Light Lv. 5 - 25% boost Enormously boosts critical hit rate</item>
	<item>Flashing Blade Lv. 5 - 120% boost Enormously boosts critical hit damage</item>
	<item>Flashing Spirit Lv. 5 - 3~6 BC Critical damage enormously boosts BB gauge</item>
	<item>Hymn of Awakening Lv. 3 - 100% boost Hugely boosts BB Atk</item>
	<item>Legendary Calamity Lv. 4 - 100% boost Hugely boosts elemental damage</item>
	<item>Warrior's Command Lv. 5 - 5-10 BC Probable enormous BB gauge boost when attacking normally</item>
	<item>Empress's Heartbeat Lv. 4 - 2-4 BC Probable huge BB gauge boost when attacked</item>
	<item>Prosperous Nobility Lv. 4 - 20% boost Hugely boosts efficacy of BC</item>
	<item>Healer's Revelation Lv. 4 - 1,200 + 10% Rec Hugely recovers HP each turn</item>
	<item>Angel Tears Lv. 4 - 25% chance to heal 20% damage Probable huge recovery of HP when attacked</item>
	<item>Demonic Victory Song Lv. 4 - 4 BC Hugely boosts BB gauge each turn</item>
	<item>Hyperion Lv. 4 - 40% boost Hugely boosts HC efficacy</item>
	<item>Treasured Abode Lv. 4 - 25% boost Hugely boosts BC, HC drop rate when attacking</item>
	<item>Thief's Warning Lv. 5 - Enormously boosts 20% boost Zel, 10% boost Karma, 3% boost Item drop rate when attacking</item>
	<item>Legendary Thief Lv. 4 - Hugely boosts 8% boost BC, HC, Zel, 4% boost Karma, 2% boost Item drop rate when attacking</item>
	<item>Tale of Honor Lv. 4 - 40% boost Hugely boosts OD gauge fill rate</item>
	<item>7★</item>
	<item>Tablet of Ruin Lv. 7 - 100% boost to Atk</item>
	<item>Tablet of Protection Lv. 7 - 100% boost to Def</item>
	<item>Tablet of Healing Lv. 7 - 100% boost to Rec</item>
	<item>Tablet of Vitality Lv. 7 - 100% boost to max HP</item>
	<item>Destroyer's Authority Lv. 5 - 50% boost to max HP, Atk</item>
	<item>Guardian's Authority Lv. 5 - 50% boost to max HP, Def</item>
	<item>Warrior's Authority Lv. 5 - 50% boost to Atk, Def</item>
	<item>Divine Oracle Lv. 5 - 30% boost to Atk, Def, Rec, max HP</item>
	<item>Supreme Spirit Lv. 5 - 75% boost Enormously boosts Atk, Def, Rec when HP is full</item>
	<item>Supreme Ardor Lv. 5 - 75% boost Enormously boosts Atk, Def, Rec when BB gauge is full</item>
	<item>Divine Life Lv. 5 - 50% boost Enormously boosts Atk, Def, Rec when HP is over 50% full</item>
	<item>Divine Wisdom Lv. 5 - 50% boost Enormously boosts Atk, Def, Rec when BB gauge is over 50% full</item>
	<item>Demonic Life Lv. 5 - 100% boost Enormously boosts Atk, Def, Rec when HP is under 50% full</item>
	<item>Demonic Nature Lv. 5 - 100% boost Enormously boosts Atk, Def, Rec when BB gauge is under 50% full</item>
	<item>Glorious Life Lv. 5 - 0.75% boost per 1% HP remaining Enormously boosts Atk, Def, Rec relative to how high remaining HP is</item>
	<item>Rebellious Blood Lv. 5 - 1% boost per 1% HP lost Enormously boosts Atk, Def, Rec relative to how low remaining HP is</item>
	<item>Raging Light Lv. 5 - 50% chance to fill 2~6 BC Probable enormous BB gauge boost from Spark damage</item>
	<item>Raging Spirit Lv. 4 - 1~4 BC Spark damage hugely boosts BB gauge</item>
	<item>Raging Core Lv. 5 - 30% boost Spark damage enormously boosts BC, HC drop rate</item>
	<item>Hymn of Awakening Lv. 4 - 150% boost Enormously boosts BB Atk</item>
	<item>Legendary Calamity Lv. 5 - 120% boost Enormously boosts elemental damage</item>
	<item>Demonic Victory Song Lv. 5 - 5 BC Massively boosts BB gauge each turn</item>
	<item>Empress's Heartbeat Lv. 5 - 3-5 BC Probable enormous BB gauge boost when attacked</item>
	<item>Prosperous Nobility Lv. 5 - 25% boost Enormously boosts efficacy of BC</item>
	<item>Healer's Revelation Lv. 5 - 1,500 + 10% Rec Enormously recovers HP each turn</item>
	<item>Angel Tears Lv. 5 - 25% chance to heal 25% damage Probable enormous recovery of HP when attacked</item>
	<item>Hyperion Lv. 5 - 50% boost Enormously boosts HC efficacy</item>
	<item>Legendary Thief Lv. 5 - Enormously boosts 10% boost BC, HC, Zel, 5% boost Karma, 2% boost Item drop rate when attacking</item>
	<item>★★ Special elgif 1/1 acc</item>
	<item>Divine Tree's Memories - Fills 2BC each turn &amp; boosts 15% BC, HC drop rate when attacking</item>
	<item>Divine Flame's Memories - 20% boost to Atk &amp; boosts 10% BC efficacy</item>
	<item>Divine Darkness's Memories - Boosts 10% critical rate &amp; absorbs 5~8% dmg when attacking</item>
	<item>Goddess' Protection - Invalidates all status ailments</item>
	<item>Holy King's Devotion - Negates all status ailments, elemental damage, critical damage</item>
	<item>Great Pioneer's Light - 20% boost to all parameters, boosts 50% Spark damage and Fills 1~2 BC on Spark</item>
	<item>Epidemic God's Tragedy - Adds 10% Curse/Poison/Paralysis, 13% Injury/Weak/Sick to attack &amp; enormously boosts 150% damage against status inflicted foes</item>
	<item>Imperial Encouragement - Fills 5 BC after each turn &amp; fills 4-5 BC when attacking normally &amp; negates Def ignoring attacks</item>
	<item>Heavenly Recollection - 20% boost to Def, max HP, 20% chance 25% damage reduction &amp; 30% chance to heal 10-15% damage &amp; 40% chance to fill 2-4 BC when attacked</item>
	<item>Demolishing Blade - Critical damage boosts Fills 3-5 BC, enormously boosts 150% critical damage and 25% hit rate &amp; 50% boost to Atk</item>
</exskills>
